













JACKSON NODA

Web & Mobile App Developer

PERSONAL STATEMENT

As a passionate and professional Software Engineer with over 8 years of experience in web and hybrid/native mobile app development, I've built various kinds of web and mobile apps related to Healthcare, Fitness, E-learning, Social Networking, E-commerce, Wallet, etc. Also. I've been working in startup and fortune 500 companies for several years. I want to use my challenge for various kinds of projects and want to get long term clients to extend their business together. I'm a strong problem solver and always provide top notch production until 100% satisfaction.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Jun 2019 - Mar 2021

Full Stack Engineer • Contractor • ICOTOP

- ✓ Built responsive UI based on the UX/UI design with ReactJS
- ✓ Designed AWS CloudFormation templates to configure automatically all resources required by the project
- ✓ Implemented AWS automated deployments from GitHub to AWS (CodeBuild, CodeDeploy, ECS, Docker)
- ✓ Created NodeJS web service with 10+ external API integrations, automated tasks, and public endpoints
- ✓ Automated solutions to process company contacts/referrals, alert scheduling system, SMS notifications to sales reps and more, sales pipeline webhooks, and more
- ✓ Developed Restful APIs and hosted as AWS Lambdas



Feb 2018 - Apr 2019

Frontend Developer • Contractor • FanHero

✓ Integrated TDD using Jest and Enzyme by checking components inside the React application.



- Worked with UI frameworks like Material UI to build responsive pages
- Used declarative language, Typescript, for better error handling in large applications.
- Utilized storybook to test individual react component's functionality.



Nov 2016 - Jan 2018

Mobile App Developer • Contractor • OpenArc, LLC.

- ✓ Designed and developed various kinds of native and hybrid mobile apps with Swift/Java/Kotlin/Flutter/React Native that were downloaded over 20K times within the first three months after publishing.
- ✓ Improved product quality through code reviews, writing effective unit tests and collaborating with QA on implementing automation testing

SKILLS



































LANGUAGES

- ✓ English (Fluent)
- ✓ Japanese (Fluent)



Jun 2015 - Oct 2016

Full Stack Lead Developer • Contractor • 101 Management, Inc.

- ✓ Built a PWA using MERN stack while collaborating with Senior Software Engineers via zoom meetings multiple times a week
- ✓ Used Agile Software Development practices to plan > build > test > deploy > gather feedback > and refactor projects
- ✓ Built multiple, and well-tested RESTful APIs using Node.js with Express, Mocha, Chai, and Supertest



Sep 2013 - Jun 2015

General Contractor • Contractor • Sunshine Homes, LLC.

- ✓ Developed new server-side features for REST API Microservices including data models, API controllers/handlers and DB querying with Ruby on Rails and PostgreSQL for heavy use of Streams
- ✓ Utilized Docker and general functional programming style to minimize branching and improve maintainability
- ✓ Tested with RSpec



PROJECTS

Festival Foods

Every business decision they make is based on the question, "Will it bring the customer back?"

Worked On: Vue, Vuetify, Vuex, Nuxt Link: https://www.festfoods.com

SVAcademy

This project was that fast-track users into a customer-facing career in tech with one of our 400+ employer partners.

Worked On: React, Next, Typescript, Node, Express, GraphQL, Vercel

Link: https://sv.academy/apply

NFT Art Trading

This project was to build a webapp that trades NFT Arts.

Worked On: React, Typescript, Redux, Material UI, Ruby on Rails, Postgres, Docker

Link: https://www.satoshi.art

Magazine For Wellness

This project was to build a magazine for wellness.

Worked On: HAML, Ruby, JQuery, Bootstrap, Rails, Postgres, Nginx

Link: https://www.ewellnessmag.com

Mobile Apps

- Social Networking App (React Native)

 $\frac{https://apps.apple.com/us/app/jumprope-how-to-videos/id1265394316}{https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.jumprope.android&hl=en&gl=U\\S$

- Wallet App (React Native)

 $\frac{\text{https://apps.apple.com/us/app/exodus-secure-crypto-wallet/id1414384820}}{\text{https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=exodusmovement.exodus&hl=en&gl}} \underline{= US}$

EDUCATION



University of Florida, [Gainesville, FL] 2009 - 2013
Bachelor's degree in Computer Science & Engineering



Florida Southern College, [Lakeland, FL] 2007 - 2009 Computer Science & Engineering